There are some people
who see aging naturally
as nothing but humiliation.
Confirming.
How much did this woman spend
only to end up with such a pathetic face?
A gold mine that's been fully exploited.
And yet,
they never seem to learn their lesson.
After multiple surgeries
in an attempt to stop the aging process,
and with a face
over-saturated with hyaluronic acid,
this patient can
no longer smile naturally.
Ms. Anna, we will
bring your smile back, I promise.
I know you will. I have faith.
You'll feel a little prick.
There.
Still hoping to regain her smile,
she made the shocking decision
to go under the knife yet again.
How insecure can she be?
You gotta check out this new club.
Who's that?
Isn't she super cute?
- Huh? I don't know.
- Good morning.
Out of all living creatures,
only humans try to defy
the laws of nature.
Hina.
Tanaka, oh my…
No way.
I mean, my goodness!
It's like I'm looking right at Nastassia!
Wow.
You look so great!
Fighting your natural appearance,
refusing to age…
What is there to gain from that?
- Gauze.
- Here.
Suction, please.
No matter how hard
you fight against nature,
you pay a price, one way or another.
Enough already.
Those guys are totally staring at you.
Don't worry about it.
Hey, guess what?
VOICE ACTOR AUDITIONS
I signed up.
Sorry, but you missed the cut-off.
He said he'd make an exception for me.
Oh wow, that's excellent!
Can I ask a favor?
You think you could give me
a little dance lesson?
The debt payments have all been processed.
However, since her father's debts were
accrued with an illegal lender,
we took all the necessary measures
to conceal our involvement.
Is she even planning
to show up to work today?
Oh.
I believe she's coming in
for Dr. Rui's surgery this morning.
Surgery on her first day?
She said she would like to sit in on it.
- Excuse me? Doctor?
- Hm?
I noticed the way
you're using your scalpel.
Um, the superior labial artery…
- Take over.
- Yes, Doctor.
Suction.
- Tanuma, come with me.
- Okay.
- Do you have something to say?
- Sorry.
It's just that you handled the scalpel
in a way that could nick the artery.
Do you know how many surgeries
our clinic does in a year?
Way more than any
third-rate teaching hospital.
Is a doctor's skill measured
by the number of surgeries they do?
What was that?
So you're saying,
no matter how much experience you have,
a surgeon can never improve?
Director.
Hm.
If that's what you're saying,
why don't we have you perform the surgery?
What?
I think we're all curious
to see if you're capable.
No, I won't.
And why not?
Because I'm a doctor.
I won't operate on someone who isn't sick.
Mm.
I'm relieved that's how you feel.
Dr. Numata,
we're glad to have you here.
I think you'll fit in very well.
What does that mean?
In our world…
everyone we treat is sick.
CLINIC VICE-DIRECTOR
RUI KOMIYA
Sorry for the delay.
- It's no problem.
- So, what do you think?
I feel like I'm in Kabukicho.
We sure aren't here to entertain guests.
Anyway, just to fill you in,
we've got three clinics in Tokyo.
Our flagship clinic in Roppongi,
one in Shinjuku, and one in Shibuya.
The main clinic is Roppongi
is just the director and me.
In other words, I'm one of the best
cosmetic surgeons ever.
But, Tanuma, pretty soon--
Are you doing this on purpose?
My name is Numata.
I don't really care what your name is.
Here.
- Take off your mask.
- What?
There are no clients here. Do it.
Take a look.
You look like you're pissed off
at the whole world.
Patients don't want to see that.
First, just take a breath.
Relax the spot between your eyebrows.
Better. And now,
lift up the corners of your mouth.
LIFT THOSE LIPS
All right, we'll work on it. Let's go.
Yes, understood.
- Hello.
- Oh, hello.
So this is the medical office.
- Just like a teaching hospital, right?
- No. It's completely different.
Hm?
Well, I'm guessing
you didn't have sales quotas.
But on the bright side,
the pay is unlike anything else.
They're all such money-grubbers.
I mean, professional doctors are supposed
to be above material things like that,
aren't they?
Don't you agree?
It's your own fault for expecting ethics
from a plastic surgery clinic.
They hire their doctors
straight out of school.
No residencies, no internships, and yet
they let them do high-risk surgeries,
paid for by insurance,
with zero experience.
That doesn't mean
they're not still good doctors though.
Get this.
Their reviews are all way too positive
to be real.
They gotta be paid for.
This is our media PR department.
They control our online presence.
Normally, a third party would do it,
but the director insists
that it be done internally.
The internet is still a wild west.
It just takes one keyboard warrior
to destroy your reputation.
Was that directed at me?
They hire people
to flood their page with positive reviews.
If there's anything negative,
they rush to have it taken down.
Honestly, it's not that different
from what the mob does.
Honestly, I'm just surprised
that you're so surprised, Dr. Numata.
What?
And here is our production department.
They handle everything video-related.
Subtitles, editing…
This is the
"Name 100 Cosmetic Procedures" challenge!
Our Head Nurse, Ms. Todoroki.
If you're confused about anything,
she'll help you out.
Feel free to ask anything.
And that includes anything on Dr. Rui.
I know everything from his income
to who he's slept with.
Uh-oh.
All jokes aside, though,
we've been following
the backlash you've been facing online.
We were saying how tough it must be
to see your character dragged like that.
While you're here, us on the nursing team
will do everything we possibly can
to help you feel comfortable,
and forget about that mess.
Oh. Thank you very much.
- I look forward to working together.
- Mm.
- What did you think of her?
- Oh, her?
I thought she was nice.
I'm a bit relieved.
I was feeling like a fish out of water.
Hm. You should know, Ms. Todoroki was
very close to Kanabun before her death.
Even outside of the office.
What? You're only telling me this now?
Wow, what are the odds
we end up with Dr. Backlash?
But she's gotta be good, right? I don't
think she would have been hired otherwise.
- Mm.
- She won't last long here anyway.
Because I won't let her.
Through here is the VIP section. A special
area hidden from the general public.
It's like a ninja house.
Celebrities, politicians,
anyone high profile,
can enter through here
without being seen out front.
Hey, Mr. Hikita.
No employees allowed back here.
He's also one of our doctors.
We refer to him as Mr. Spot Remover.
Spot Remover?
Wait. I… I didn't see his name out front.
Mm. You wouldn't.
He's actually on the dark side.
The dark side?
No online presence.
No interaction with patients. He just
scrubs in and scrubs out. That's it.
What kind of cosmetic surgeon
doesn't use social media? Unreal.
He can't understand that not
all doctors want to be on social media.
Says they're on "the dark side,"
like they're villains.
The whole thing is so discouraging.
If you hate it that much,
then why did you even agree to work there?
Is the money that good?
That's part of it.
But
it's absolutely clear as day,
they're responsible for Kanabun's death,
and I'm gonna prove it.
Whoa. You're gonna be a whistleblower.
Not exactly.
Hey, why do you always have sunglasses on?
Uh…
I mean, does it matter if I see your face?
Well, the thing is,
I'm actually still healing.
Are you okay?
I can't anymore.
This song's too hard. I can't.
No, come on. You totally had it!
Why didn't I ever train seriously
as a dancer?
Be kind to yourself.
You've got an amazing voice.
That alone is good enough
to get you all the way. Right?
Nice job.
- Thank you.
- Ms. Tanaka, may I have a word?
- Yeah.
I was looking over your résumé
for the audition.
- Are you… using a stage name?
- Oh.
- Stage name?
- Uh…
Mashiro Himenoki. Oh!
- Great choice!
- Oh, thank you!
"Yoshiko Tanaka" just felt
plain and boring, you know?
I thought… Am I allowed to?
Hm. This is a first.
I've not seen many students do this.
But it's clear
you're taking this seriously, so
sure, it's fine.
Thank you so much.
Well, in that case,
I should choose one too.
Your real name
is already a movie star name!
Oh! Fumi's here!
Uh, why did you order sushi?
We told the regulars
that all our debt was paid off,
and they insisted on celebrating.
Have a bite, Fumi.
- Oh.
- This is the good stuff.
- Oh my.
- It's expensive.
Of course, naturally.
- Damn straight.
- Fumi.
We'd like to thank you, your mother and I.
As a father,
I'm so honored
to have a daughter like you, honey.
- Thanks a lot.
- That's so sweet.
- I'm gonna cry.
- Stop it, or you'll make me cry too.
- All right.
- Listen up, everyone.
Thanks to Fumi here,
we've all been given
a second lease on life!
Everyone, drink!
Fumi, come on.
Come have one drink with us at least.
Not now. I'm tired.
Wait, Mom,
you're not drinking alcohol, are you?
What about your cirrhosis?
That could be fatal.
I'm drinking tea, okay? Lay off.
- Oh, really?
- That's right.
Hey, make sure
Takashi understands the full story.
The debt isn't gone.
It was taken over by someone else.
Oh yeah, so who took over the debt anyway?
- What?
- Who took over the debt?
I'm your mother. I deserve to know.
We should bring them a gift or something
to thank for their generosity.
No. Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
- Whoa, what?
- Uh…
A senior doctor in private practice,
he took it over.
But he doesn't want any fuss made.
He wants to stay anonymous.
It's not like you were ever that much
of a mother before, so why start now?
Hey. Where's Takeru?
Oh, him. He doesn't seem
to want to come out of his room at all.
Honestly, both you and Takeru,
you two can be so antisocial.
Wow, really?
- Come out when you're ready.
- What?
FUMI NUMATA HAS BEEN ARRESTED, RIGHT?
SEEING HER NAME MAKES ME SICK
JUST SEEING HER NAME MAKES ME SICK
Takeru?
Takeru.
What's wrong?
You okay?
There's sushi downstairs.
I'm not hungry.
What is it?
What's going on?
I came here to see your charming face.
Show me that smile.
How am I supposed to smile right now?
Mm, you know what they say.
How when you smile,
it can make you happier, or whatever.
Look.
You look like you're pissed off
at the whole world.
Whatever.
Smiling isn't gonna help anything.
Yeah.
Well, I'm gonna go take a shower.
You're telling the truth?
Hm?
About Kanabun.
I did everything in my power as a doctor.
Okay.
- First, cleanse.
- All right.
- Next, we'll suture.
Wait. The silicone.
She asked us to put it back.
What? What's the point?
That tumor's gonna have to come out.
Okay, suturing now.
The director will be in the clinic
all day today.
We have several procedures on the books,
so I'll be assisting.
Dr. Takada and Dr. Hamada from Shinjuku
will offer their support
with first-time and returning patients.
- Yes.
Numata, you'll be assisting them.
- Okay.
- Also--
I think…
Numata will assist me
on the surgery today.
What?
Dr. Rui, you have patients who will
require your time, so this works out.
All this in one day?
The director is often away
doing TV interviews and lectures,
so they squeeze in as much as possible
on the days she's here.
Scalpel.
- Let's lift the right side a little.
- All right.
I knew it. You are good.
Right. Next.
Are we cutting
the orbicularis oris muscle?
- Precisely.
- Okay.
Seeing as there is space
to work with on your face overall,
I suggest that the first thing we do
is smooth out this section
on your nasal bridge with hyaluronic acid.
It should give you much better balance.
I can also see that you have
dark circles under your eyes.
Let's add some volume there,
which will brighten…
Okay, next.
Uh, are you doing
my liposuction correctly?
Of course. Yes.
Dr. Numata,
we have a procedure that requires
full anesthesia this afternoon,
so make sure
to be back from lunch by 12:30.
That's only ten minutes!
Good, huh?
What, my cigarette?
Not that. I'm talking about her surgeries.
What?
I've watched a lot of her surgeries,
and I still find it amazing.
I guess it's in her genes.
That woman's earned her reputation
as The Hand of God.
Yeah, but surely there are other doctors
just as gifted as she is, right?
- Dr. Tanuma--
- Numata.
Oh.
I'm… I'm sure you probably
feel like a hypocrite working here,
but… but just know,
you keep your head down,
do as you're told,
you can become obscenely rich.
Just go with the flow.
Don't question things.
"Dark side." Yeah, right.
Are you all right?
I'm a doctor. Can I take a look at you?
Here, let me see.
Take deep breaths.
Just rest here for a moment.
I… I'm fine. I just need to get a taxi.
- No, just sit here for a bit.
- I'm fine. Thank you.
Taxi. I need to get a taxi.
- Don't go.
- Yes. Thank you.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
Dr. Numata,
why don't you do the next surgery?
- What?
- Don't worry. I'll be assisting.
Come on, that's ridiculous.
You're already familiar
with the procedure,
since you saw what I did on Kanabun
when you removed her implant.
It's not the same.
Putting them in
is easier than taking them out.
A plastic surgeon actively practicing
should be able to do this procedure
with their eyes closed.
Got him.
- Nice throw.
- Oh shit.
KILLER PSYCHO DOCTOR SENTENCED TO DEATH
Damn, that's cold.
Right, let's get started.
Numata's operating?
A breast augmentation.
Can you believe it?
All right, now make an incision
along the marker.
Yes, I know.
- Two-pronged retractor, please.
- Here.
- Insertion sleeve, please.
- Yes.
Dr. Numata?
Yes, sorry.
- Here.
- Okay.
I'll finish everything else up.
You complete the medical paperwork.
Okay.
Make sure you're thorough.
Include as much detail as possible.
I'm very pleased.
You're just as good as they said you were.
PARTNER MODEL AGENCIES
NATURÉ
KANA KOKUBUN
MALIGNANT TUMOR FINDINGS
ENTER PASSWORD
Mm.
- Ms. Miwa?
- Yes?
I'm trying to complete my charts,
but do you know the password?
Uh, sorry, only the doctors know that.
- Oh, okay.
- Yeah.
Thank you.
Make room. Out of the way, please.
Thank you so much.
Stand aside, please.
Let us pass. Coming through.
Come on, let's go.
Ms. Tanaka!
Ms. Tanaka! Phone call for you.
It sounds like an emergency.
Can I get your autograph, please?
Please, just one selfie? Please!
Don't scare me like that!
I thought something had happened to Dad.
I had to.
You wouldn't have picked up otherwise.
Besides, your dad isn't doing well.
I need you to come back to run the shop.
It's too much for me.
What, do you want me
to drop out of school? Is that it?
Don't be like that.
People like us can't just climb the ranks.
Not in this world.
You can't keep living in a fantasy.
I can do it!
Just please let me try.
Please.
Yoshiko…
We need all participants
to head to the main hall now.
- Yoshiko!
- Yes!
An outing?
Yes.
The whole staff
goes out together once a month.
The director wanted to make sure
you were invited.
- Oh, that's not really my thing--
- Come on!
It's a chance
for us to get to know each other.
Ah.
Okay, I'll check it out.
Fantastic.
Ah, just one more thing from the director.
It's really important
nobody recognizes you.
The backlash, you know?
Mm. For sure.
I'll do that.
- Wow, is that another new bag?
- Mm-hmm.
Wow, that's so cute.
How many do you have?
Hm. It's a secret.
KABUKICHO ICHIBANGAI
- Customers!
- Welcome.
Hey.
Welcome. First time?
Didn't see this coming.
VOICE ACTOR AUDITIONS
Next up, Mashiro Himenoki,
a third-year student
in the voice acting department.
Oh, thank you.
Excuse me.
I'm Ryuga.
May I?
Are you recovering?
Oh. Yeah, actually.
I just finished healing my nose.
Oh.
I see.
Does everyone who works here
get work done?
I don't think
there's anyone left who hasn't.
You have to keep up to survive.
- Keep up?
- Mm.
Oh, wait. Are you new there?
You don't know
our club is partnered with Tohyama?
Oh. Right. Of course.
Yeah, that makes sense.
You can't imagine the number of customers
we've referred to you guys.
I was able to get my nose done
at a 50% discount.
Oh.
Hey. You can't drink alcohol.
Aren't you recovering?
- Oh.
- Isn't that bad for you?
The alcohol disinfects.
You can go ahead
and introduce yourself now.
Uh…
Mm… Uh…
Um…
Uh…
I'm going to…
read this letter to my family.
Your family?
Because, well,
I think that true voice acting…
relies on reading.
"Dear Dad."
Mm.
"Thank you."
"Dear Mom."
"Thank you for raising me, even though
I'm not anything special."
"But…"
"…I still…
want to say to both of you…
that the time has come to say goodbye."
Welcome, partners
of the Tohyama Clinic Group.
- The Hand of God!
- Yeah!
Congrats! Their highest quarter yet!
"Not to sound overly dramatic…"
"…but I've…
become someone totally new."
"I'm no longer
the sad little girl you once knew."
"And I'm
a better, stronger, braver person,
no longer hiding away!"
Let's have the best night ever!
- Let's go!
- Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
- Yeah! Kings! Queens!
- Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
"I have been reborn
into a wonderful…
dazzling, beautiful, amazing new world!"
"And I have…
decided that this is the world
I'll live in."
"Mom and Dad…"
"…just know…
that it breaks my heart…"
"…to leave you behind. I'm sorry."
"But
it is here on this stage…
that I shall now give you
this final goodbye."
"I shall soar in the sky
like a butterfly!"
"I shall fly off to this brand-new world,
so beautiful and exciting."
"So farewell."
"I love you."
"Goodbye…
Mom and Dad."
"Farewell
to my old self."
Numata?
Hey, are you okay?
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Stop. You're drunk.
- Why are you even here?
- You haven't answered your phone or texts.
You're getting it all over me!
- Okay, you're all right.
- I'm sorry. I'm fine, I swear.
- Leave me alone.
- No way.
- I'm not leaving you.
- Bye-bye!
- What the hell? Come on.
- Get your hands off me.
So you're working for a plastic surgeon?
Not gonna lie. I'm honestly surprised.
Yeah, duh.
I still can't believe I'm doing it.
They take advantage of our insecurities.
And they make us think beauty is the only
thing that could possibly matter.
Disgusting.
I guess.
Still, sounds like it's the fastest way
to get your dad out of hot water
and fix his money troubles.
Don't you guys get paid
so much more than a regular doctor?
Come on. Cut yourself some slack.
You can always come back
once you've figured things out.
Look, what I mean is,
I'll be there for ya.
If you ever need to vent, you call me.
We'll get a drink.
"Total Beauty?"
Yes. We have a patient on the books today
for this package.
The director asked me to make sure
that you had the necessary information.
A full-body makeover?
Yes, the patient leaves everything
up to the director, from head to toe.
It's the most deluxe treatment package
we offer here.
Come in.
Excuse me.
Ms. Sakashita is here for her appointment.
Oh, hello.
It's lovely to meet you.
Thank you for seeing me.
It's an honor to be here.
We shall now announce our five finalists.
First,
Hinano Tachibana.
Yes!
Wow!
- Yurina Toyama.
- Yes!
Great.
- Sakura Shinomiya.
- Yes.
- Saki Kashima.
And lastly,
Mashiro Himenoki.
Tanaka.
Oh. Y… Yes.
Did you forget your own stage name?
Sorry.
Ms. Hiiragi spoke very highly
of your audition.
What?
- She did?
- That's right.
In the final round, they'll be scoring
your singing and dancing abilities,
so make sure you all practice.
Yes.
All right,
I'm starting to paint a picture.
Now, regarding your budget,
Altogether, it looks like your package
will cost at minimum… this amount.
5 TO 7.5 MILLION
- No problem. I trust you, Doctor.
- I'm glad to hear it.
Well, we'll take a few photos
and draw a little blood.
Okay.
- Show her to the changing room.
- Of course. Right this way.
- Right in there.
- Okay.
- You can take a seat.
- Oh. Yes, of course.
Sorry. I'm just a little nervous
since this morning.
I even forgot
to take my pills.
I'm so forgetful these days.
OPSO ORAL SOLUTION 5 MG
Excuse me.
- Morphine?
- Yes.
I saw her take the pills myself.
I guess she has a serious condition
she hasn't told us about.
She nearly collapsed outside
the other day.
Besides, I don't think her body
is strong enough to handle surgery.
I understand.
I'll decide if she's a good candidate
once her blood work is in.
Okay.
- One minute.
- Of course.
Morning, Dad. Can I help you?
I'm sorry to bother you at work.
It's just that, uh,
I heard a rather strange rumor.
I wanted to double-check it with you.
- What rumor?
- I'm not saying that it's true…
Uh, there's talk that the Tohyama director
made a critical medical error,
and that a lot of clients, uh,
are leaving for other clinics.
Oh, you can't be serious. Come on, Dad.
Don't tell me you believe those lies.
Why don't you talk to our accountant?
We're making even more money now
than when you were running the show.
That's what I thought.
It's just a silly rumor. You know people
will say anything to try to drag me down.
That's all there is to it.
I have to get back to work.
However, that being said,
the fact that you can't
nip these rumors in the bud,
doesn't that mean you're losing your cred?
Oh, don't be ridiculous, Dad.
Our sales are great.
We're not losing anything.
I've still got my reputation
as The Hand of God.
Don't worry.
That's good.
Well, I'm glad
I got to hear it from you directly.
Mm. Yeah.
Dr. Tohyama?
Oh. I'm so sorry.
This question is from
a woman in her seventies.
She'd like to know if there's an age limit
for plastic surgery.
Well, it depends on the procedure itself.
However, I do think that any procedure
can be conducted safely on elderly people.
Doctor, are you all right?
You seem a little off today.
That's because you haven't
asked me to dinner today, Hamaguchi.
Hey, that's not fair.
You never come when I do ask.
But for real, are you okay?
I'm absolutely fine.
- Okay.
- Wait.
- I was wondering…
- Yes?
You once said that you'd be interested
in doing a documentary on the clinic?
Oh, yeah, I'd love that.
An inside look on plastic surgery.
A documentary that shows patients and
doctors as their most authentic selves.
Mm. So…
I might have an angle for you.
Yeah, yeah, that's right.
Opso. Five milligrams.
Oh, I see.
Uh, if they're on Opso
and they're suffering hair loss,
then that definitely points to cancer.
And if we factor in their advanced age,
surgery would be a huge strain,
so I imagine
that they're now in palliative care.
That's what I thought.
Yeah.
Takeru.
What are you doing?
Well, you're the one
who said smiling makes you feel happier.
- Huh?
- Yeah, I Googled it.
Apparently, there's some truth to it.
Just lifting the corners of your mouth
can improve your friendships.
So, you're just gonna be smiling 24-7?
You know,
I'm thinking about eyelid surgery.
- What?
- I think it would look good on me.
Oh! Dr. Tohyama.
- I'm sorry to be bothering you this late.
- It's fine.
I just wanted to discuss something.
- Oh?
- This is Mr. Inoue, our legal advisor.
- Won't you come in?
- Thank you so much.
Yes, thank you.
FILMING FOR A TV PROGRAM BEGINS TODAY
What's going on here?
Watch those cables.
We need to get this lighting set up.
They're filming one of our clients
for a Total Beauty documentary.
A Total Beauty client?
No, it can't be…
Hey, what are you doing?
I'm sorry. I don't have time right now.
You said you'd wait for Ms.
Sakashita's test results before deciding.
What were they?
It doesn't matter. I already know.
She has terminal cancer.
And if she does?
You know what will happen if you
operate on someone in that condition.
And now you're filming her?
What are you thinking?
- Takashina, her consent form.
- What?
She told us herself directly
about her cancer diagnosis.
She still agreed to both the surgery
and the documentary.
I ACCEPT THE OUTCOME, WHATEVER IT MAY BE
So you're going to exploit her
as a publicity stunt?
Don't be so dramatic, Dr. Numata.
She has consented to be filmed.
They won't film any surgery that may
require general anesthesia, so drop it.
So, you're fine
just giving her whatever she asks for?
If she says she wants to die, you'll just
kill her? Have you lost your damn mind?
Hm.
Someone who doesn't have much time left
is asking for one last chance
to be beautiful!
My duty is to help people like her.
Life isn't just quantity.
It's also quality.
There are ways to help
besides chemotherapy.
I'm not cut out for this.
Yeah, and don't I know it.
I was hoping you'd rise to the occasion.
By all means, quit if you'd like.
Of course,
you will regain all your debt
if you do that.
How was that?
That was amazing!
- Yay!
Thank you!
That was so good, Tanaka!
Oh, Mr. Kudo.
What is it?
Well…
Ms. Tanaka, we need to talk.
Uh…
You're gonna blow the whistle on Tohyama?
How are you gonna do that?
I looked at Kanabun's medical
records. There were signs of a tumor.
Which means the director already knew
about the tumor when she operated on her.
I have full access
to these records. It's proof.
So it'd be like an anonymous leak?
That could get some traction.
Also, I found a folder
for that modeling agency.
I can expose that document too.
Okay, then. We'll leak it on my page.
Oh, but wait, what about all your debt?
Oh, well,
I'll figure that out.
Don't worry about it.
- Dr. Hikita.
- Mm.
- Hi.
Uh… Hey, you know the files
containing the surgery data?
- Yeah.
- Would you mind telling me the password?
What?
- Why would you need that?
- Oh.
It's just that the director
wants me to study your previous surgeries.
She never told me the password.
Oh.
So you decided to go through with it, huh?
- Is it cool that I asked you?
- Yeah.
- Forfeit?
- Mm.
But I don't understand. Why would I quit?
Well, it seems we've got an issue.
- What? What kind of issue?
- Listen.
Ms. Hiiragi received an anonymous message
claiming you were sugar dating
to pay for your plastic surgery.
Her manager called me immediately.
She's concerned.
Agencies are uncomfortable
with that kind of thing.
- But--
- I know. I know.
I know this is hard.
Listen. Here's my advice.
If you drop out,
it's not an admission of guilt.
I know it's hard.
You can try out again next time.
I won't do it!
I won't. I'm not gonna drop out!
Please think about the school.
This agency collaboration could benefit us
so much. We need the audition to go well.
If I fail at this, I'll have nothing left.
If they find proof of your actions,
you could jeopardize the chances
of any future students, and then what?
You could ruin the--
Is everything okay?
Are you fighting about something?
Hm.
You did it.
It was you, wasn't it?
What do you mean?
How… How…
- How could you do that?
- Stop! Get off. Hey!
- How could you do this to me?
- Ow!
Hey, girls, stop it!
Why? How could you?!
PARTNER MODEL AGENCIES
USER ACCESSING PROTECTED FILE
HIKITA
Mr. Hikita?
Takashina!
Yes?
- It was you! No one else knew about it!
- Get off!
I know it was you! What is wrong with you?
- Knock it off!
- You're crazy. Let me go!
You free?
- I'm free.
- Excuse me!
Hey! Numata, watch where you're going.
- Knock it off! Break it up already!
- Get off of me!
You scratched me!
You can go to hell!
I never want to see you again!
- You just thought I'd beat you!
- You beat me?
You're delusional!
Stop!
Quiet!
You'd lose.
You can't even dance.
It'd be way too easy to beat you!
Are you struggling with something?
Your new self
begins right here.
Turn that dream into reality.
You can be reborn.
The Hand of God
can change you.
Do it for yourself.
Are you satisfied
with who you are right now?
Everyone…
deserves to be beautiful.
Tohyama Cosmetic Surgery Clinic.
Who were you going to send these to?
A tabloid, I guess?
All right.
Let's cut the bullshit.
First of all, Numata, stealing
confidential information is a felony.
Punishable by jail.
Are you even listening to me?
Director, may I have a word?
Not right now.
It's important, Director Tohyama,
I assure you.
It's okay. We can fix this.
I promise. It's going to be okay.
- Ms. Tanaka?
- Dr. Rin!
Oh, Doctor, please!
- Please tell me you can fix this!
- Ms. Tanaka, just calm down.
- You have to do it!
- Prepare her for surgery.
- Yes.
- Okay.
- Fix me, please!
- Relax.
It'll be okay.
Okay, just breathe.
Ms. Tanaka, I know you're in pain,
but please listen.
I promise you I will fix your nose, okay?
It'll be fine.
But for that to happen,
you'll need a very long recovery.
No, please!
I have the final round
of auditions next week.
- You can try again next year.
- No it has to be this year!
I won't get this chance again!
Please!
I have to win.
Doctor…
Director.
You're really going to do this surgery?
She wants to do this audition.
She'll be swollen and bruised.
How can you in good conscience do this?
You know what could happen if you put
a prosthesis in. She's at high-risk for--
- Do you have a better plan?
- Yes, first repair the broken bone.
Wait for it to heal.
It's the medically responsible
thing to do.
I can't do a procedure she doesn't want.
Then let me do it.
Can I go talk to her?
Ms. Tanaka?
Do you remember me?
Katsushika Hospital.
I remember you very well, Ms. Tanaka.
And what your face looked like before.
I used to work in the ER.
So, as you can imagine,
I've worked on a lot of facial injuries.
I will do my absolute best
to help fix your injury.
You have my word.
So my recommendation
is that we first restore your nose
to its original state.
VIOLET EIKAEN
TEMPORARILY CLOSED
FOR PERSONAL REASONS
Yoshi?
Yoshi!
You came back. I can't believe it!
We got him through the worst of it,
but he still hasn't
regained consciousness.
I know he would have wanted you here,
so I begged the doctor
to let me bring him home.
Before the stroke,
he was looking forward to teaching you
how to run the business.
To spend time with you.
Sweetie.
She came back.
Yoshiko is here, darling.
So please get better soon.
You have to show her the ropes
at the store.
I'm sorry.
Mom…
I…
I can't give up on my dream. Not yet.
But…
what's gonna happen to the store then?
I'm not Yoshiko Tanaka now.
I am Mashiro Himenoki. All right?
I'm sorry.
I have to…
live the life I want in Tokyo.
You can't.
Please don't give me my old nose.
Why not?
- You can audition next year--
- It's not about the audition.
I just can't.
Please, I can't bear
to have that face again.
If you do that…
I will kill myself.
The surgery…
changed my life in the best way.
I was finally able
to live to the fullest without fear.
I want Dr. Rin to fix it.
I…
I won't let you do my surgery.
Why don't we fit that new procedure
in once you have some time for recovery?
Oh yes, please.
Sounds good, Kotomi.
I'll see you next week.
All right. See you next week.
Oh, just to fill you in,
Ms. Tanaka will be able
to attend her audition after all.
I managed to get it postponed.
Pays to have friends in high places.
All I did was ask Kotomi
to give Ms. Tanaka another chance.
The rest will be up to Ms. Tanaka.
One other thing.
If you wouldn't mind, Doctor,
it would go a long way if you could
take that scowl off your face.
It's the murderer's brother!
Where are you going?
Hey, get back here!
Hey! Answer us!
You're running off
to go kill someone too. Is that it?
Whoa. Why is he smiling?
Yeah, weird. He's a total psycho!
Oh damn, run! I can't get caught again!
How you been?
Okay, now let's get a close-up.
Wow, look at her.
Her skin's hanging off her bones.
Think she'll be okay?
She better not die halfway through.
The whole project would be scrapped.
Come on. Don't joke around like that.
Okay. That's all we need here.
Great work. That's all we need
for pictures today, Ms. Yuriko.
They'll do your interview next.
- Go ahead and get changed.
- Okay.
KANA KOKUBUN
MALIGNANT TUMOR FINDINGS
DELETE ALL FILES?
DELETED